<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blogs on echo4eva</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blogs on echo4eva</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 12:00:56 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/hugaur/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>pomogomo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/pomogomo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 12:00:56 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/pomogomo/</guid>
      <description>writeup While reading &amp;ldquo;Learning Go: An Idiomatic Approach&amp;rdquo; by Jon Bodner, I used a pomodoro app on my phone that I found really neat to track my time. The only thing that I didn&amp;rsquo;t like about it is that it didn&amp;rsquo;t count excess time once the countdown reached zero, so I decided to make my own as a side project to practice Go.&#xA;A blogpost by a good mutual @kennethnym on Twitter titled &amp;ldquo;the art of programming and why i won&amp;rsquo;t use llm&amp;rdquo; shaped my approach for this project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>east coast writings</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/east-coast-writings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 12:00:56 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/east-coast-writings/</guid>
      <description>Collections of writings (2)&#xA;realization Thursday was a great day. I visited New York City on a frigid night and ate at this amazing Korean restaurant. They served a foot-long rolled egg omelet that melted in your mouth like ice cream. As the evening wore on, the touristy charm began to fade away. I suddenly felt a tightness around my neck like I was being dragged along getting yanked from store to store.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>spawn die spawn die</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/spawn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 11:25:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/spawn/</guid>
      <description>i was feeling really sad last night. i was on call with Black, Blue, and Pink for 4 hours. i caught up with them, talked about random stuff, and made up blatant targeted rules for their drinking game all while realizing i was in my bed, 2413 miles away, staring into the popcorn ceiling.&#xA;it was so fun! i haven&amp;rsquo;t felt this way since the last time we all hung out irl last year, i felt human.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>my social anxiety story</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/my-social-anxiety-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 11:25:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/my-social-anxiety-story/</guid>
      <description>hi its kinda crazy how i have 1k oomfies following me. it&amp;rsquo;s not really about the goal of reaching it; it&amp;rsquo;s just that past me could never imagine. even if it did happen back then, i wouldve been scared to interact with or tweet to that amount of people. i used to be so frightened being perceived by people, knowing who, and how i am.&#xA;nowadays, i dont really care anymore, just a tiny bit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>my one pager</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/my-one-pager/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:25:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/my-one-pager/</guid>
      <description>a one pager is about your life, who you are as a person and what your goals are, it&amp;rsquo;s a living document and an extension of yourself. knowing these 2 things and being true to them is what can make someone happy! after watching a ted talk from REDACTED about this and listening to them over Teams today, i wanted to try it out and make my first iteration including author notes (99% of the blog) and make it public!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>insecurities</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/insecurities/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:25:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/insecurities/</guid>
      <description>preface: i love documenting my life. i like to describe myself as a former shut-in that’s taking their first steps into the real world. i’ve had remote college for 3 years, my internships were only remote, and my side gigs were remote too. i basically been living online through my college years (which is a blog for another time, fuck covid). i haven’t dealt with real life personal problems until now, insecurities being one of them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>caffeine voibes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/caffeine-voibes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 11:25:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/caffeine-voibes/</guid>
      <description>i drink so much caffeine, i like to drink hot coffee, matcha, and especially viet ice coffee. i don’t like energy drinks as much, but they’re there. after switching the drinks around, i notice that different types of drinks i crave depend where i am in my life.&#xA;hot coffee hot coffee just gives me comfy vibes. i dont drink these as often anymore, but every time i do i’m probably playing an RPG or grinding an MMO on a winter morning with the windows open.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>le peak</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/le-peak/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 21:54:02 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/le-peak/</guid>
      <description>i finally climbed to the top of the mountain that i’ve laid eyes upon, it’s hard to breath. there’s a mysterious lavender scent that keeps my breath steady, but there’s no flowers here. where is it coming from? i feel like i can climb higher but there’s nothing ahead or above me other than the night sky and some comfortable clouds. this is where i am mentally after recovering from the shutdown of two energizing vietnamese ice coffees, while my physical self is trapped in a room cluttered by exhaustion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>yapping starting to live</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/yapping-starting-to-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 15:12:15 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/yapping-starting-to-live/</guid>
      <description>intro after two decades, i’m finally starting to live my own life. its a huge step with tiny increments inside. im starting to do what i want, go where i want, and eat what i want. for you it might be normal to go to an event out of interest, go to the park to take in your favorite weather, or going out of impulse to satisfy a craving. for me, i used to always control, set prerequisites, and limit myself from doing so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the hiatus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/the-hiatus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 12:00:56 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/the-hiatus/</guid>
      <description>the hiatus What happened? It&amp;rsquo;s been about 2 months since my last blog and a lot has happened. To summarize, I’ve been learning a lot. I learned about ML in tabular data by utilizing random forests and neural nets, feature engineering, differential calculus, mathematical and conceptual details of neural and convnets, interviewing skills, and currently the YOLO (You Only Look Once) algorithm.&#xA;Two months may seem like a short timeline but it felt so long.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>nlp and lms</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/nlp-and-lms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 12:00:56 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/nlp-and-lms/</guid>
      <description>talking metal box How could a computer even talk to us? How is it possible it can answer any question you give it (with questionable correctness)? Here’s a better question, how could a computer understand language, especially english? It’s very simple, natural language processing, thanks for reading. Seriously, it’s really simple.&#xA;what is natural language processing? Natural language processing, NLP for short, is how a computer can understand language. It’s a process that has a number of steps and components in order for it to work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>deep learning, first epoch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/first-epoch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 12:00:56 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/first-epoch/</guid>
      <description>My First Epoch whoami Greetings, my name is Jericho Imperial, currently a 4th year CS undergrad who is addicted to the drug called “self-studying deep learning!” I’m technically a 4.5th year undergrad, because I am one class short even though my school let walk on stage and didn’t notify me of this issue beforehand, but anyways, welcome to my first “academic” blog about deep learning! Here’s a lot about me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>hello world!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/hello_world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 12:00:56 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hugaur/hello_world/</guid>
      <description>welcome! hey this is my first blog ever! i initially made this website to write about whatever i learned in fastai since they recommended it, but i’ll probably write about whatever else i’m learning, my projects, thoughts in tech, and maybe thoughts in general. this website is my 3rd website ever made and 1st project made with svelte. so far i love how svelte is with their routing, it just seems super intuitive and easy.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
